[音乐]
[MUSIC]
&gt；&gt；Douglas Crockford：预防人类的最简单的攻击
&gt;&gt; Douglas Crockford: The simplest attack to prevent people
从获得出版物，&gt；&gt；Douglas Crockford：这是我们
from getting publications, &gt;&gt; Douglas Crockford: Is this one where we
简单地订阅什么都不用。
simply subscribe with nothing.
这意味着我们将把未定义的推送到订阅者数组上。
So that means we're gonna push undefined on to the subscribers array.
所以当我们做这个循环的时候，对吗？
So when we go to do this loop, kaboom right?
所以每个跟在我们后面的人都不会收到任何信息。
And so everybody after us doesn't get any messages sent.
那你怎么解决这个问题？
So how would you fix that?
&gt；&gt；演讲者2：这不是问题，因为在你之前的人
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: That's not the problem though, because the people before you
仍然得到它，所以-&gt；&gt；Douglas Crockford：对，但是
still get it, so- &gt;&gt; Douglas Crockford: Right, but
之后的人不会这样做，所以-&gt；&gt；演讲者2：问题是我们试图
the people after don't, and so- &gt;&gt; Speaker 2: The problem is we try to
防止任何人-&gt；&gt；Douglas Crockford：我们必须确保
prevent anyone- &gt;&gt; Douglas Crockford: We have to make sure
每个人都会收到每一条信息。
that everybody receives every message.
如果一个人得到了它，我们不能说我们成功了，但是
If one person gets it we can't say that we've succeeded, but
每个人都必须得到它。
everybody has to get it.
&gt；&gt；扬声器3：你可以对我的标签进行类型检查，对吗？
&gt;&gt; Speaker 3: You can just do a type check for your tag on me, right?
&GT；&GT；道格拉斯·克罗克福德：我们可以这样做。
&gt;&gt; Douglas Crockford: We could do that.
在这里，我们可以做类型检查，如果类型等于函数。
Up here, we could do type check you know, if type of equals function.
&gt；&gt；扬声器4：您应该用里面的内容重新包装您的呼叫。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 4: You should be re-wrapping your call in a try catch with what inside.
&gt；&gt；Douglas Crockford：是的，因为如果他们要传递任何函数
&gt;&gt; Douglas Crockford: Yeah, that's it because if they were to pass any function
这抛出它不会这样做，所以-&gt；&gt；扬声器5：so pubsub
that throws then it wouldn't do that, so- &gt;&gt; Speaker 5: So pubsub
是我们给予所有人的东西-&gt；&gt；Douglas Crockford：我们给予
is something we give out to all the- &gt;&gt; Douglas Crockford: We give
对于所有第三方，他们都共享该实例。
to all the third parties, they all share that instance.
&gt；&gt；扬声器5：所以在这种情况下，它实际上有点不信任用户输入。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 5: So really in this case it's kind of don't trust user input.
&gt；&gt；扬声器5：他们可以发送给订阅者，但是
&gt;&gt; Speaker 5: They can send to subscribers but
他们可以向您发送一个作为订阅者的函数，一个空字符串。
they can send you a function as subscriber, an empty string.
&gt；&gt；Douglas Crockford：对，好吧，在这种情况下，它可能是一个恶意的失败，但是
&gt;&gt; Douglas Crockford: Right, well, in this case it could be a malicious failure but
也可能是意外故障。
it could also be an accidental failure.
有些人可能会简单地错误地将其命名为
Someone might simply call it incorrectly and
我们不希望整个系统因此而失败。
we don't want the whole system to fail because of that.
所以这就是try接球的目的，对吗？
So this is what try catches for, right?
所以我们可以简单地抓住这个东西，忽略错误，然后继续处理。
So we can simply catch the thing, ignore the error and we'll keep on processing.
所以，这很好。
So, that's good.
所以我们现在准备好接受你的第二次观察了。
So we're now ready for your second observation.
&gt；&gt；Speaker 4：将SUBSCRIBE设置为NULL。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 4: Set subscribe to null.
&gt；&gt；Douglas Crockford：是的，所以我们可以篡改pubsub实例本身
&gt;&gt; Douglas Crockford: Yeah, so we can tamper with the pubsub instance itself and
我们可以删除属性。
we can delete the properties.
将它们之一更改为undefined或null，或用其他函数替换它们
Change either of them to undefined or null or replace them with other functions
这可能会做一些更阴险的事情，比如只允许某些人订阅或
that could do things more insidious like allow only certain people to subscribe or
允许人们认为他们订阅了，而他们没有订阅。
allow people to think they subscribed when they didn't.
或在发布消息时对其进行过滤，或
Or to filter the messages when they publish, or
为了在消息发布时篡改消息，
to tamper with the messages when they publish,
在这个主题上有无数可怕的变化。
there's an infinite number of terrible variations on this theme.
那你怎么解决这个问题？
So how would you fix that?
&gt；&gt；扬声器6：使用服务器。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 6: Use a server.
&GT；&GT；道格拉斯·克罗克福德：你说什么？
&gt;&gt; Douglas Crockford: I'm sorry?
&gt；&gt；扬声器4：所以你不会真的公开发布所以
&gt;&gt; Speaker 4: So you aren't gonna really expose publish so
非常像，&gt；&gt；扬声器4：您是
much as, &gt;&gt; Speaker 4: You're
将返回一个函数。
gonna return a function.
你要返回一个函数。
You're gonna return a function.
返回函数？
Returns a function?
&gt；&gt；扬声器4：我不知道。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 4: I don't know.
它就像是一个getter和setter。
It's something like a getter and a setter.
如果他们只能得到，你不会想设置它的。
You're don't wanna set it if they can only get it.
&gt；&gt；Douglas Crockford：你可以，但有一件事比那更容易做。
&gt;&gt; Douglas Crockford: You could, but there's an easier thing to do than that.
&gt；&gt；扬声器7：冻结此处的选项？
&gt;&gt; Speaker 7: Freeze the option here?
&gt；&gt；Douglas Crockford：是的，你想冷冻它。
&gt;&gt; Douglas Crockford: Yeah, you wanna freeze it.
因此，如果我们冻结对象，那么所有这些攻击都是完全失败的。
So if we freeze the object then all of those attacks are completely frustrated.
&gt；&gt；Speaker 4：你现在会用JavaScript做这个吗？
&gt;&gt; Speaker 4: Would you do this right now in JavaScript?
&gt；&gt；Douglas Crockford：是的，S5中增加了冻结。
&gt;&gt; Douglas Crockford: Yeah, freeze was added in the S5.
&gt；&gt；扬声器4：好的。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 4: Okay.
&gt；&gt；Douglas Crockford：所以它在IE9，10和11中
&gt;&gt; Douglas Crockford: So it's in IE 9 and 10 and 11 and
所有好的浏览器。
all the good browsers.
这样我们就可以冻结了。
So we can freeze.
这样就完全解决了这个问题。
So that completely solves this.
所以这就是为什么我喜欢把冻结作为一种物体构造的原因之一
And so that's one of the reasons why I like freeze as an object construction
模式，因为有很多东西我们永远不用担心
pattern because there's a whole lot of stuff we'll never have to worry about
如果物体被冻结。
if the objects are frozen.
冻结这个物体并不会削弱它的能力
And freezing this object does not impair its ability
去做它应该做的事。
to do what it's supposed to do.
这些方法仍然可以访问订阅者数组，并且
That these methods still have access to the subscribers array and
仍然可以做所有那些动态的东西。
still can do all that dynamic stuff.
只是没有人可以篡改实例。
It's just nobody can tamper with the instance.
&gt；&gt；Douglas Crockford：好的，我们现在准备好接受你的下一个建议，
&gt;&gt; Douglas Crockford: Okay, we're now ready for your next suggestion,
你的第一个
your first one.
&gt；&gt；扬声器4：我已经忘了。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 4: I forgot it already.
&gt；&gt；Douglas Crockford：[笑]&gt；&gt；扬声器4：我们要进去了。
&gt;&gt; Douglas Crockford: [LAUGH] &gt;&gt; Speaker 4: We're gonna pass in.
我们将订阅一个删除功能，
We're gonna subscribe with a function that deletes,
遍历此操作并删除所有内容。
iterates through this and deletes everything.
&GT；&GT；道格拉斯·克罗克福德：是的，没错。
&gt;&gt; Douglas Crockford: Yeah, exactly.
&gt；&gt；扬声器4：差不多吧。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 4: Something like that.
&gt；&gt；Douglas Crockford：是的，差不多吧。
&gt;&gt; Douglas Crockford: Yeah, something like that.
所以应该是这样的。
So that'd be something like this.
所以我们要订阅一个可以访问这个的功能。
So we're going to subscribe with a function which will get access to this.
然后我们可以访问订阅者阵列。
And then that gives us access to the subscribers array.
因为这是一个方法调用，即使它看起来不像一个方法。
Because this is a method invocation, even though it doesn't look like a method.
我们调用一个存储在数组中的函数，
We're calling a function that is stored in array,
我们不认为这是一个方法调用，但JavaScript认为是。
we don't think of that as being a method invocation but JavaScript does.
所以从现在开始一切都会和这个联系在一起。
So everything from here on will get bound to this.
因此在本例中，我们将把this.length设置为0。
So in this case, we're going to set this.length to 0.
这将删除所有订阅者，但
That will delete all of the subscribers but
我们也可以做更阴险的事情。
we could do much more insidious things as well.
同样，如果您对此对象执行以下操作，则您可以对该对象执行的坏事数量是无限的
Again, there's an infinite number of bad things you can do to this object if you
拿到这个。
get access to this.
&gt；&gt；Douglas Crockford：所以这又是一个很大的困惑来源，对吗？
&gt;&gt; Douglas Crockford: And so this is a big source of confusion again, right?
在JavaScript中，带括号的东西是方法调用，但是
That in JavaScript, things with brackets are method invocations but
我们不认为这些是方法调用。
we don't see those as method invocations.
所以再一次，这是一种混淆，导致对我们的
So again, this is a confusion which leads to misunderstanding of what our
程序是这样做的，这使得漏洞和安全漏洞的发生成为可能。
programs do, which make it possible for bugs and security exploits to happen.
&gt；&gt；Speaker 4：在您刚才编写的这个函数中，
&gt;&gt; Speaker 4: Inside this function that you've just written,
这是支付子对象，对吧，
this is the paysub object, right,
有了var订阅者，这就是它的范围，对吧？
with its var subscribers, that's its scope, right?
&gt；&gt；Douglas Crockford：不，在这种情况下，这是订阅者数组。
&gt;&gt; Douglas Crockford: No, in this is case, this is the subscribers array.
因为这就是方法。
Because this is the method meant.
好的，这是你的函数，你把它传递给订阅。
Okay, so here's your function, you pass it in to subscribe.
因此它被存储在订阅者数组中。
So it gets stored in the subscribers array.
在这个循环中，它现在被调用，但它被作为一个方法调用。
And in this loop, it now gets called but it's being called as a method.
在这种语言中有四种方法可以调用方法。
There are four ways to call a method in this language.
我认为应该只有一个，但有四个。
I think there should only be one, but there are four.
并且至少有一种形式对于它是哪种调用感到困惑。
And at least one of the forms is confusing as to which kind of invocation it is.
&gt；&gt；Douglas Crockford：那你怎么解决这个问题呢？
&gt;&gt; Douglas Crockford: So how would you fix that?
&GT；&GT；扬声器7：我的大脑说呼叫，不？
&gt;&gt; Speaker 7: My brain says call, no?
&GT；&GT；道格拉斯·克罗克福德：你说什么？
&gt;&gt; Douglas Crockford: I'm sorry?
&gt；&gt；扬声器7：我的大脑说使用呼叫。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 7: My brain says using call.
&gt；&gt；Douglas Crockford：如果我们说，
&gt;&gt; Douglas Crockford: That would be one way to do it if we say,
订户[i]点调用，然后传入。
subscribers[i] dot call and then pass in that.
这是一种方法。
That would be one way to do it.
&gt；&gt；Douglas Crockford：我更喜欢的方式还是
&gt;&gt; Douglas Crockford: The way I would prefer to do it or
您可以做的另一件事是将Subscriber[i]分配给局部变量，
the other thing you could do is assign subscriber[i] to a local variable,
然后调用该变量。
and then call that variable.
或者，我们可以做的是使用for Each。
Or, what we could do is use forEach.
我现在一般不信任for循环，我更喜欢for each。
I'm now distrustful of for loops in general and I like forEach much better.
所以我可以传递给forEach一个函数，它将调用函数的每个元素，并且
So I can pass to forEach a function which will call each element of the function and
忽略任何例外，我真的很喜欢这一点。
ignore any exceptions and I really like this.
我觉得这非常好。
I think this is very, very nice.
所以我不再使用for loop了。
So I'm not using for loops anymore.
我在做这件事，因为它正在过去
I'm doing this stuff instead and because it's passing
在每个单独的元素中，关于如何调用这一点没有混淆。
in each individual element, there's no confusion about how this gets called.
它永远不会是一个方法调用。
It's never gonna be a method invocation.
实际上，这个函数甚至看不到数组。
In fact, this function doesn't even see the array.
它所看到的都是个别的元素。
All it sees are the individual elements.
&gt；&gt；演讲者4：提醒我们如何逃脱每一次。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 4: Remind us how to escape forEach.
&GT；&GT；道格拉斯·克罗克福德：你说什么？
&gt;&gt; Douglas Crockford: I'm sorry?
&gt；&gt；演讲者4：提醒我们，如何突破forEach。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 4: Remind us, how do you break out of a forEach.
&gt；&gt；Douglas Crockford：您使用Each而不是ForEach。
&gt;&gt; Douglas Crockford: You use every instead of forEach.
我们会设计它，使这个函数总是返回true。
And we would design it so that this function would always return true.
&gt；&gt；Speaker 4：返回false，然后离开。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 4: It returns false then it leaves.
&gt；&gt；Douglas Crockford：那么是的，假的是退出信号。
&gt;&gt; Douglas Crockford: Then yeah, false is the exit signal.
&gt；&gt；扬声器8：在上一张幻灯片中，
&gt;&gt; Speaker 8: On the previous slide,
有人想让你澄清为什么这指的是数组。
somebody wants you to clarify why does this refer to the array.
&gt；&gt；Douglas Crockford：对，这就是函数
&gt;&gt; Douglas Crockford: Right, so this is the function
在这里被处决，好吗？
that is being executed here, okay?
这种形式的函数调用就是方法形式。
And this form of function invocation is the method form.
方法表单中将有一个点或一个括号。
The method form will have a dot in it or a bracket in it.
所以，所有在最后一个点左边的东西
And so, everything to the left of the last dot or
最后一个括号绑定到这个
last bracket gets bound to this and
这就是为什么会发生这种事。
that's why that happens.